Anusha ABBURI

Date of birth: 09/06/1996 | **Gen:** Female | (+49)15235828702 | anushaabburi96@qmail.com

Gebruder-Grimm weg 6, Buxtehude

About me: I have total 4+ years experience as a Power Bi developer and Senior Systems engineer as a System tester, to be able to work as System test Engineer or Power BI Developer in a world- class organization where my in-depth will be greatly utilized to achieve maximum performances of the company. My endeavour and dedication in the job will be helpful in achieving the company's goals and objectives.

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2022 - October 2023 Hyderabad

Power BI Developer - Infosys.

- I have experience working with Power BI and other BI tools to create dynamic and visually appealing reports and dashboards that help organizations make data-driven decisions.
- I am proficient in data modeling, data visualization, and data analysis, and I have experience working with various data sources such as Excel. SQL Server, and Azure.
- I am also well-versed in data governance and data security best practices, and I am comfortable working with data in a highly regulated environment.

Skills: Data Analysis, Data Warehousing, Business Analysis, Reporting, Microsoft Power Query, Dashboards, DAX, SQL, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft SQL Server.

August 2020 - May 2022 Hyderabad

Senior Systems Engineer - Infosys.

- Provides technical support identifying, investigating, and resolving users problems with Test Applications.
- Create test solutions and support other test engineers in projects Ensure the test solution robustness for sustainable manufacturing Contribute automated tests as needed for our continuous integration pipeline.
- Maintaining the Database Uptodate in steady Environment.
- Fixing the Bugs and Hot fixes.

Skills: Manual Testing, Portals, Soap UI, FileZilla, Putty, Jira, Microsoft Excel, Virtual Computers.

September 2019 - August 2020

Research Analyst - Factset.

- Research analysts examine and validate the accuracy of the data to ensure that it produces meaningful information.
- Analyze data. Upon collecting the data, research analysts use mathematical, statistical and analytical models to find patterns that may reveal business opportunities
- Analyze data using statistical software. Identify trends and make recommendations to improve.

Skills: Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Office, Microsoft Word, Notepad++, Microsoft Excel

June 2017 – August 2018 – Hyderabad, India

SYSTEM VALIDATION ENGINEER - Tech Mahindra

Project: Infotainment System

Responsibilities: The infotainment system in the vehicle is a combination of information and entertainment delivery to drivers and passengers. It uses Audio/video interfaces, touchscreens, Keypads, USB, Bluetooth, and other types of devices. In this Infotainment USB, Bluetooth, car play, and Android Auto feature functions are tested on the Validation test Bench. It is a CAN-based validation of the interaction of the Audio ECUs. It is developed in a Canoe simulation

environment.

Tools, Protocols, and Hardware: CAN, CANoe tool, JIRA, FHOSTsp, IBM DOORS, Excel, Sharepoint.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Aug 2017 - May 2019 - Hyderabad, India
MASTERS IN BUSINESS MANAGEMENT - JNTUH University

August 2014 - April 2017 - Rajamahendravaram, India BACHELOR OF SCIENCE AND COMPUTERS - AKNU UNIVERSITY

ORGANISATIONAL SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Python
- ∘ HTML, CSS
- Operating Systems: Windows XP/7/10, Linux, IOS
- ∘ Tools: Vector Canoe, RTC (IBM Rational Team Concert), IBM Doors, CAN, Eclipse, Jira.